http://openconcept.ca/privacy-policy

OpenConcept
AboutWho we areOur ValuesCommunityCareersServicesOur WorkDrupalNewsEventsBlogsNews ReleasesContact Us
Main menuAboutServicesOur WorkDrupalNewsContact Us
Privacy Policy
OpenConcept Consulting Inc. (OpenConcept) is a Certified B Corporation that works with open source software. We care about your privacy! As a Canadians we have complied with
The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). We support the privacy initiative of the European Union's General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
OpenConcept will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location-based information. We do sometimes ask for your name, address, email, phone number.
Why we need your data
We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with on-going organizational updates and funding information and analysis services in line with this overall contract. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you. As a service company, we need to know who are clients are and how to best communicate with them.
Because we are collecting your data, we take extra care with our security. We ensure that all of our sites can be accessed through secure HTTPS protocols. We actively maintain the security on both our website and the server that it sits on. Furthermore, we have moved our servers to Canada to reduce the route taken by packets from our site to the bulk of our users.
What we do with your data
All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in Canada however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within Canada. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data. When using our site, you may be asked to provide personal information about yourself. OpenConcept Consulting Inc. will only use this information for which such information was requested. We will not share, rent, sell or lease your personal information to any unaffiliated person or entity without your express consent.
We also use MailChimp to occasionally send newsletters. We have ensured that all of our lists are GDPR compliant. If you do not wish to receive them, please use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter.
Cookies are pieces of information stored by your web browser that make it easier to interact with our site. JavaScript is a programming language that allows for a more dynamic browsing experience. We use cookies & JavaScript to deliver a better user experience. You may disallow cookies and/or JavaScript in your web browser, although it may have impacts on the site’s appearance and functionality. We never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our website.
We use 3rd party tools like Google Analytics to evaluate the traffic on our website. We have configured these tools to minimize the data that they collect.
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you for the duration of a session.
How long we keep your data
If you are a customer of OpenConcept, Canadian tax law requires that we keep basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 7 years after which time it will be destroyed. Any information you give us for marketing or promotional purposes we will keep until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.
What we would also like to do with your data
We would, however, like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This information is not shared with third purposes and you can unsubscribe at any time via phone, email or our website.
What are your rights
If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and have it corrected or deleted. You may review for accuracy and update any personal information we have about you. To do so, please contact us. We respect Canada's PIPEDA & Europe's GDPR.
If you wish to raise a complaint about how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated, contact support@openconcept.ca.
Interested in digital accessibility? Sign up today to our monthly Accessibility Action Newsletter!
613-686-6736 (OPEN)
info@openconcept.ca
Careers
FOLLOW US
AboutServicesOur WorkDrupalBlogContact UsAccessibilityUsage PolicyPrivacy
